&gt；&gt；steve：它起作用了，但很明显，现在你可以足够聪明了，而且
&gt;&gt; Steve: It worked, but clearly, and
now you could be smart enough, and
你可以像我将有一个请求动画帧来统治他们所有。
you could be like I'm gonna have one
request animation frame to rule them all.
但是，就像，在很多情况下，使用抽象在很多时候是有用的。
But like, in a lot of these cases, it's a
lot of times useful to use an abstraction.
我真的很喜欢一个叫Fast Dom的
One I really like is one called Fast Dom,
就像它的整个工作就是想弄清楚这些东西并让它变得更快。
like its whole job is to like figure
this stuff out and make it fast.
和Fast DOM，有一些方法，但是
And Fast Dom effectively,
there's a few methods, but
你只关心两个人。
there's only two that you care about.
测量和变异，对，有效地读然后写。
Measure and mutate, right,
which are effectively read and then write.
这是一个相当小的图书馆。
It's a pretty small library.
如果你真的想，你可以自己写这个库。
If you really wanted to,
you could write this library yourself.
基本上你调用Measure Bunch几次，它需要所有这些函数，对吧？
Basically you call measure bunch of times,
it takes all of those functions, right?
然后请求一个动画帧，在其中播放所有的变异。
And then requests one animation frame
where it plays back all of your mutates.
因此，您可以测量一系列时间，然后可以安排所有的写入
So you can measure a bunch of times,
then you can schedule all of your writes
很多次，它会把一个请求动画帧放在一起，然后
a bunch of times, and it will put together
one request animation frame that will then
一次完成所有你想做的事情。
play through all the things
you want to do at once.
它会阻止你在底部看到的所有黄色尖刺
Which will stop all of those little
yellow spikes you saw at the bottom of
火焰图。
the flame graph.
好吧所以
All right, so,
我要试一试。&gt；&gt；steve：带它去兜风。
I'm gonna give that one a shot.
&gt;&gt; Steve: Take it for a spin.
所以在这里我只想说fast dom.measure。
So here I'm just going
to say fastdom.measure.
不，实际上我是在上面说的。
No, actually I say that up top.
所以我们继续，给它一个匿名函数，我们将测量。
So we'll go ahead, give it an anonymous
function, and we'll measure.
&gt；&gt；steve：我们进去，然后
&gt;&gt; Steve: And we'll go in here, and
我们会变异。&gt；&gt；steve：酷，
we'll mutate.
&gt;&gt; Steve: Cool,
让我们试一试。&gt；&gt；steve：好的，
let's give it a shot.
&gt;&gt; Steve: All right,
又好又光滑。&gt；&gt；Steve：让我们
nice and smooth.
&gt;&gt; Steve: Let's
看看我们这里有什么。
take a look at what we have here.
别这样。&gt；&gt；steve：对，
Stop that.
&gt;&gt; Steve: Right,
你看我们不再有那些小钉子了。
you see we don't have all
those little spikes anymore.
安排动画帧，我们正在做Fast DOM正在进行调用。
Schedule the animation frame,
we're doing Fast Dom is making its call.
我们确实需要重新计算一大堆东西。
We do have to recalculate
a bunch of stuff.
显然，这不是免费的。
Clearly, that's not free.
我们在这个屏幕上有很多盒子。
We have a lot of boxes on this screen.
我们继续画，对吧？
And we go ahead and we paint, right?
但你可以看到我们并不是一下子就像，
But you can see that we're
not all of a sudden like,
我们没有所有这些动画帧的尖峰。
we don't have all those spikes
from all those animation frames.
我们用过图书馆。
We've used the library.
我们都安排好了。
We've scheduled everything.
我们可以走了，对吧？
We're good to go, right?
所以很多时候使用一个工具可以解决很多这样的问题。
So a lot of times using a tool will go a
long way to solve a lot of these problems.